{
    "subject": "resource/The_Heart_Specialist_(1922_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_silent_feature_films",
    "human_readable": "The Heart Specialist (1922 film) is about American silent feature films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6142913699150085,
            "question": "What type of film is 'The Heart Specialist'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5273761749267578,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Heart Specialist'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45074889063835144,
            "question": "Is 'The Heart Specialist' a sound film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41913551092147827,
            "question": "When was 'The Heart Specialist' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41805198788642883,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Heart Specialist'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3754878342151642,
            "question": "What country are the filmmakers of 'The Heart Specialist' from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3381944000720978,
            "question": "What is the main genre of 'The Heart Specialist'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27982932329177856,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'The Heart Specialist'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20416046679019928,
            "question": "Where can you watch 'The Heart Specialist' today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19130493700504303,
            "question": "Was 'The Heart Specialist' a success at the box office?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Heart Specialist (1922 film) is about American silent feature films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you watch 'The Heart Specialist' today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in 'The Heart Specialist'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main genre of 'The Heart Specialist'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7220_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information supports that \"The Heart Specialist\" (1922) was an American silent drama film, which aligns with the query stating it is about American silent feature films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes a 1922 silent film called \"The Heart Specialist\" directed by Frank Urson and starring Mary Miles Minter. It also mentions a later film titled \"The Heart Specialist\" that appears to be a contemporary comedy featuring Brian White, Zoe Saldana, and Wood Harris.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because The Heart Specialist (1922 film) is actually about a young woman named Rosalie Beckwith, not American silent feature films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}